Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Visit of H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan President of United Arab Emirates to Pakistan May, 1972
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with Zulfikar Ali Bhutto greeting members of the Pakistani delegation., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Officials; Men; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Royalty; Presidents; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Microphones; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Ceremonies; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Pakistan; Airports
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting an Emirati ambassador in Pakistan., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Royalty; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Tents; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Pakistan; Airports; Ceremonies
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting members of the Pakistani delegation., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Microphones; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Ceremonies; Airports; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Presidents; Sheikhs; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Pakistan
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting members of the Pakistani delegation, with Zulfikar Ali Bhutto in the background., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Men; Group Portraits; Carpets/Rugs; Airports; Uniforms; Military assistance, American -- Saudi Arabia; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Facial Hair; Women; Ceremonies; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting members of the Pakistani delegation, with Zulfikar Ali Bhutto in the background., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Carpets/Rugs; Ceremonies; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Sheikhs; Hats; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Facial Hair; Airports
  - Zulfikar Ali Bhutto pouring H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan a cup of tea, with H.E. Sheikh Rashid Bin Hamdan Al Maktoum in the background., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Furnishings; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Pakistan
  - From the middle clockwise: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Zulfikar Ali Bhutto, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, five unidentified men, H.E. Mana Al Otaiba, H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem, eight unidentified men, and H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid speaking after the arrival of the Emirati Delegation., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Microphones; Group Portraits; Men; Furnishings; Pakistan; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Tea/Coffee; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Drinks/Beverages; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting Zulfikar Ali Bhutto at the Pakistani palace., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Head Covers/Veils; Pakistan
  - From the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.E. Mana Al Otaiba, and Zulfikar Ali Bhutto at a gathering., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Pakistan; Gatherings; Officials; Presidents; Sheikhs; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Facial Hair
  - Zulfikar Ali Bhutto gifting an order to H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000018_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Medals/Insignia; Ceremonies; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Sheikhs; Officials; Presidents; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Pakistan; Gatherings
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan gifting an order to Zulfikar Ali Bhutto., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Presidents; Officials; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Pakistan; Paintings; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan sitting with Zulfikar Ali Bhutto., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Presidents; Officials; Sheikhs; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Medals/Insignia; Pakistan
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Zulfikar Ali Bhutto being received by the Pakistani delegation at the palace after exchange of orders., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000021_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Uniforms; Group Portraits; Men; Carpets/Rugs; Medals/Insignia; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Flags; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Pakistan; Sheikhs; Royalty; Officials; Presidents; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting members of the Pakistani delegation, and Zulfikar Ali Bhutto greeting members of the Emirati delegation, with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in the background., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000022_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Medals/Insignia; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Officials; Sheikhs; Presidents; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Pakistan
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Zulfikar Ali Bhutto looking at photographs at a gathering of the UAE and Pakistani delegations, with H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem and H.E. Mana Al Otaiba sitting on a couch in the background., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000023_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Sheikhs; Royalty; Officials; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Smoking; Cigarettes; Press Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Gatherings; Furnishings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Clocks/Watches; Pakistan
  - From the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, five members of the Pakistani delegation, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, a member of the Pakistani delegation, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Zulfikar Ali Bhutto, and Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum at dinner after the arrival of the Emirati Delegation, including Zaki Nusseibeh in the background., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000024_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Food; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Pakistan; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Officials; Gatherings; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Royalty; Waiting staff/Servers; Fez/Tarboush; Presidents
  - From the left: H.E. Ahmed Bin Suwaidi, a member of the Pakistani delegation, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Zulfikar Ali Bhutto, H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, four members of the Pakistani delegation, and H.E. Mana Al Otaiba at a dinner after the arrival of the Emirati Delegation., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000025_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Waiting staff/Servers; Officials; Sheikhs; Royalty; Presidents; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Pakistan; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Food; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Street Lamps; Gatherings; Drinks/Beverages; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms
  - Pakistani dancers performing for the arrival of the Emirati Delegation., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000026_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Dancing; Performing Arts; Costumes; Gatherings; Musical Instruments; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - A blank page in the album "Visit of H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nihan 'President of United Arab Emirates' to Pakistan May, 1972.", AD_MC_093_ref7_000027_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Zulfikar Ali Bhutto being received at the palace., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000028_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sheikhs; Royalty; Presidents; Officials; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Pakistan; Men; Group Portraits; Flags; Uniforms; Architecture; Ceremonies; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Carpets/Rugs
  - A group portrait of members of the Pakistani military., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000029_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Facial Hair; Horses; Animals; Pakistan; Flags
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Zulfikar Ali Bhutto, and Zaki Nusseibeh at the gifting of a falcon., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000030_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Medals/Insignia; Animals; Birds; Officials; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Pakistan; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Crowds
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Zulfikar Ali Bhutto at the gifting of a horse., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000031_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Flags; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Architecture; Horses; Animals; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Carpets/Rugs; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Medals/Insignia; Hats; Sheikhs; Ceremonies; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Officials; Royalty; Pakistan; Gatherings; Crowds
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan talking with Zaki Nusseibeh and Zulfikar Ali Bhutto during an interview, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr is in the background behind Bhutto., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000032_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Microphones; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Carpets/Rugs; Pakistan
  - From the left clockwise: H.E. Mana Al Otaiba, H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem, Zaki Nusseibeh, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr talking with members of the Pakistani delegation at a roundtable., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000033_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Politics; Group Portraits; Men; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Paintings; Government
  - From the right: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, two presidents of the nuclear plant talking with Zaki Nusseibeh, H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, and H.E. Mana Al Otaiba looking at a model of nuclear power plant., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000034_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Factories; Machines; Gardens; Officials; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Pakistan; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Presidents
  - From the right: H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem, H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, a member of the nuclear power plant, and Zaki Nusseibeh touring a nuclear power plant., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000035_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Computers; Men; Group Portraits; Factories; Machines; Pakistan; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, and H.E. Ahmed Al Sulayem (front in kandoora) and a group of men touring a nuclear power plant., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000036_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Factories; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Pakistan; Sheikhs; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Machines
  - Front: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan looking through a microscope with Zaki Nusseibeh. Back, from the right: H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem, H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, an unidentified member of the Emirati Delegation, and H.E. Mana Al Otaiba., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000037_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Machines; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Pakistan; Factories; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Officials; Royalty; Presidents
  - From the left: H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, a director of the nuclear plant, Zaki Nusseibeh, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, a director of the nuclear power plant, and H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum at a reception following the tour of the nuclear plant., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000038_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Gatherings; Furnishings; Food; Officials; Pakistan; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - On stage, from the left: Zaki Nusseibeh, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, a director of the nuclear power plant, and H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum at a reception following the tour of the nuclear plant. H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim and H.E. Mana Al Otaiba are sitting on the right., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000039_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Chandeliers; Furnishings; Men; Group Portraits; Mirrors; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Officials; Presidents; Facial Hair; Gatherings
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Zulfikar Ali Bhutto greeting representatives of the nuclear power plant., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000040_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Chandeliers; Gatherings; Group Portraits; Men; Pakistan; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Royalty; Officials; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - From the left: H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Zulfikar Ali Bhutto and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan smoking cigars, and a member of the Pakistani delegation at a dinner., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000041_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cigarettes; Smoking; Gatherings; Drinks/Beverages; Facial Hair; Bow Ties; Waiting staff/Servers; Men; Group Portraits; Pakistan; Sheikhs; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils
  - From the left: H.E. Ahmed Al Sulayem, a member of the Pakistani delegation, H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Zulfikar Ali Bhutto, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan talking with Zaki Nusseibeh, a member of the Pakistani delegation, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, a member of the Pakistani delegation, and H.E. Mana Al Otaiba at a dinner in the palace., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000042_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Men; Group Portraits; Gatherings; Waiting staff/Servers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Drinks/Beverages; Food; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Hats; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Officials; Presidents; Carpets/Rugs
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Zulfikar Ali Bhutto, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan talking with Zaki Nusseibeh, a member of the Pakistani delegation, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, a member of the Pakistani delegation, and H.E. Mana Al Otaiba at a dinner in the palace., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000043_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Uniforms; Pakistan; Carpets/Rugs; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Chandeliers; Bagpipes; Musical Instruments; Hats; Furnishings; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Men; Group Portraits; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Officials; Presidents; Bow Ties; Waiting staff/Servers; Cigarettes; Smoking; Flags; Gatherings
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan shaking hands with a member of the Pakistani delegation next to Zulfikar Ali Bhutto., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000044_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan
  - Zulfikar Ali Bhutto shaking hands with members of the Emirati Delegation, with H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Al Maktoum on the left., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000045_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Carpets/Rugs; Gatherings; Airports; Presidents; Officials; Sheikhs; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - Zulfikar Ali Bhutto waving with the Pakistani military., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000046_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Carpets/Rugs; Ceremonies; Presidents; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Pakistan; Airports; Facial Hair; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Tents
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan waving from an airplane, with Zaki Nusseibeh in the bottom left., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000047_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sheikhs; Men; Group Portraits; Airplanes; Transportation; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Clocks/Watches; Cameras; Pakistan
  - A group portrait of members of the Emirati delegation., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000048_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Carpets/Rugs; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Airports; Airplanes; Ceremonies; Transportation; Pakistan; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Buildings; English Writing
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan hugging an unidentified man outside an airplane, with members of the Pakistani delegation surrounding him., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000049_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Airplanes; Transportation; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Hats; Facial Hair; Airports; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Officials; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan talking with a member of the Pakistani delegation, next to Zaki Nusseibeh., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000050_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Pakistan; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Airplanes; Transportation; Airports; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Presidents
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan talking with members of the Pakistani delegation, next to Zaki Nusseibeh., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000051_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Hats; Facial Hair; Microphones; Pakistan; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials
  - Members of the Emirati delegation arriving in cars at the airport., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref7_000052_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 33 x 27 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)